<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Text Passage Coding Challenge</string>
    <string name="activity2_name">Second Activity</string>
    <string name="text_header">Select a passage.</string>
    <string name="text_one">Text One</string>
    <string name="text_two">Text Two</string>
    <string name="text_three">Text Three</string>
    <string name="passage_selected">Passage Selected.</string>
    <string name='content_one'> Do not stand at my grave and weep\n
I am not there; I do not sleep.\n
I am a thousand winds that blow,\n
I am the diamond glints on snow,\n
I am the sun on ripened grain,\n
I am the gentle autumn rain.\n
When you awaken in the morning\'s hush\n
I am the swift uplifting rush\n
Of quiet birds in circled flight.\n
I am the soft stars that shine at night.\n
Do not stand at my grave and cry,\n
I am not there; I did not die. </string>
    <string name="content_two">Out of the night that covers me,\n
   Black as the pit from pole to pole,\n
I thank whatever gods may be\n
    For my unconquerable soul.\n\n

In the fell clutch of circumstance\n
    I have not winced nor cried aloud.\n
Under the bludgeonings of chance\n
    My head is bloody, but unbowed.\n\n

Beyond this place of wrath and tears\n
    Looms but the Horror of the shade,\n
And yet the menace of the years\n
    Finds and shall find me unafraid.\n\n

It matters not how strait the gate,\n\n
   How charged with punishments the scroll,\n\n
I am the master of my fate,\n
   I am the captain of my soul.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="content_three">The tree that never had to fight\n
     For sun and sky and air and light,\n
But stood out in the open plain\n
     And always got its share of rain,\n
Never became a forest king\n
     But lived and died a scrubby thing.\n\n

The man who never had to toil\n
     To gain and farm his patch of soil,\n
Who never had to win his share\n
     Of sun and sky and light and air,\n
Never became a manly man\n
     But lived and died as he began.\n\n

Good timber does not grow with ease,\n
     The stronger wind, the stronger trees,\n
The further sky, the greater length,\n
     The more the storm, the more the strength.\n
By sun and cold, by rain and snow,\n
     In trees and men good timbers grow.\n\n

Where thickest lies the forest growth\n
     We find the patriarchs of both.\n
And they hold counsel with the stars\n
     Whose broken branches show the scars\n
Of many winds and much of strife.\n
     This is the common law of life.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="title_one">Do Not Stand By My Grave and Weep</string>
    <string name="title_two">Invictus</string>
    <string name="title_three">Good Timber</string>
    <string name="back">BACK</string>

</resources>